Okay, we are now going to call the order today's regular meeting of The Miami City Council for Tuesday February 2nd. Second item on either agenda is Corbyn recognition and new employees
For 4th quarter 2015 Kim
Jennings
Okay, we want to recognize tonight our new employees for the 4th quarter. We'll start with a library
They wanna come up!
Two people from The Library
Casey Cantwell and Kristen Barnes
Oh okay
Well let's talk about it
OK Cacy was born in Rice & Miami
He graduated by Miami High School
And also Indiana, Indiana with his associate sociology
He's currently in his final semester at Missouri 7th State University where he will be graduating with the graduates of General Studies
This fine, so we're glad to have Cacy on board
We need two new dispatchers
Javan Ben Kieran and Clayton Wagner
Okay
Clayton was actually hired as a part-time dispatcher
On October 27 but recently
He's been hired as a full-time dispatcher
In fact, you've January 16
Clayton has had been in law enforcement since 1994
he worked for the Ottawa County Sheriff Department
As of the Reserve Deputy
A jailer and a dispatcher
For seven years
And also work to support the city is a fairland, North Miami
Clayton has a bachelor degree in marketing
Management from Missouri 7
Okay and we've also hired two new police officers
One of them isn't here tonight
Their exparks he is at Claytony
But Alex Perez, who's here
And Alex has graduated from Miami in 2009
He had 2 children, Yamaleath
In the end Yenhalese
I just five-and one
So Alex brings a great service to our Police Department
Because Alex Is bilingual
And that is something really we realize
Alex started his law enforcement career in commerce
In 2012, first as a reserve officer
and then 2013 was hired full-time
Until
We were able to get him over two our staff
Here on Miami in December
So welcome Alex
The final person we want to recognize tonight is Denay Jenin Holt
From the community department
Demaye was born in Tacoma, Washington
And has lived on several states
She's married and she had two children
Unfortunately
But it wasn't a tragic accident
In 2009
but he also made a scholarship
And he was born in the school
The scholarship is funded by an annual fundraiser
They are both very much involved
In past six years they have been blessed to be able
To give 37,000 dollars and scholarships
For one and a hundred percent free
Thank you Cindy
I'm with that on council
You're welcome to everyone
Okay, I'm number three
As public input and unscheduled personal appearances
Is there anyone in the audience that wishes to address
The council on any of these agenda items
Mr. Roy
Thank you very much
Good evening Mayor Councilman and Councillor and City Manager Dean
Thanks
I have to be short so it must very
Quirk with my remarks on your stand the time constraint
Respect that
Must've been on terminal organizing finance agency
And i had them for 14 years
and see there are two reasons
Number one, I bear some go against staff's recommendation
About eight or ten percent of a time
Looked up all when we got nothing data
Hopefully today
We said to yesterday
Will suffice is that kind of data
The second thing about offer
Is it apparently i make the same amount as you guys do
Which isn't very much
So, thats kinda tough
I'd just like every single part
Of this process how they will milk, mitty
To select a brokeraging authority
Another agency in April can be better job than Gallagher
For our city, I should be better in correct
And i will have a request to the council
The committee of conclusion
A brief history about this we started
There's got to get it ten and half years ago
Talking blue cross because NFP
Have gone to Muscovi
Looked across as
As they architective that
Savings scoggy over four hundred and two thousand dollars
But just changing different networks from PCC to Blue Cross
Because of the discounts
So we've been trying get that done
That will be it done with Jeff
We're out at time in 2014
Will close this last year again
Ran outta town but thats a couple hundred thousand years
I know you are trying to say no, i'm not even able
No one can do so as well
I think it's the real problem
And maybe this selection committee has a site
Different in what our thoughts might be
What their thought is going to hopefully have
That will help them
Health insurance according
To day sure with Blue Cross on supply
Each of you and With his number
Is health insurance
Health insurance for cities
For manufacturers, for consumers
For a smart worker banks
For pharmacies it is still health insurance
NFP isn't excellent broker
There are excellent consultant and so
And NFP does more cities in Oklahoma
The algorithms were internationally
But local homicalgers
Choose more lives than an app
We're both all the largest
So my request is simply to have your committee
Call a day surely see if health insurance
Health Insurance and maybe they can then start
Calling some of the references
Their minor area of services with city health insurance
Such as not falling 5500
Again we had public sector, rich galarders
Out at Chicago
With the 1100 cities and helps them through all of that
But I do not believe our references were called
Although
That we're Not Cities
And i ask you to have your staff please call
Our References
Call Steve Baszure or Linda Perciam, both for one
Marcella Rathers, Curi Bany
Jason Bledons
A subair's room, listening is story
That any of you that go to Osborne's now
You would have been paying $5 for every prescription
For the rest issue, if rich had not handled
Or no other agent can give it
Because is a purchasing power
Of galarders
I ask about what we know
We've clients from Diamond
To either the city
New Corridor or Latin
And we have to either the healer, Hugo
Tulsa or Cormacini
Bixby, no matter
Grow in and you need call those people
To see what kind of job would be
If You don't think that
That will do a great job for us things
One is, at galarders
Each human measured on your retention
Of clients
And over there, Category 2
This building is a small village of office
That has the highest retention
Of any galarder's office in this south central region
Including Missouri and Museum
Mrs. Sippy, Arkansas Taxes
Obviously Oklahoma
We have to best
Because we work harder for you employees
And new clients
We work with this kind of an attitude
Try to solve their problems
More employees or our friends
With no them, some are relatives
You want it
To be your agent
So the world, health insurance
Sometimes a deafem issue in the world is confusing
A young addict
He's appeared before you, the foreign doctor
And he was in that eyes
When some school class
and met
Was trying to teach them what a profit
Finding it said
Does anybody here can be told about what a profit is
In jail-waste of the hand
His head my grandfather Lillard
Is his own profit
You sell something for more than a cost
That smile, my father, would, gentlemen
Please consider our request
We would appreciate it
Thanks Dick, by the way
Which I haven't talked about each other's speech
No idea what is going to say
Yes that you're leading
He probably do not go in a like
But i have this, good evening
My council
Friends
Most definitely
Once your all-to-knower there
Respect your positions up there
And i'd like this
Or not fun
Certainly, now I'm from me
and im all that's didn't really match her
Up there a few years ago
We had it many times as well
It is not very funny to sit back there either
So we're thought of mine
I also have some comments
That hope for the betterment
If you think they would be better heard
If i would draw author Jay Gallagher
From all of the items in item 16
Or in essence we're drawing from
The brokerage
Competition
Can you send your attention over to me, I'll do a wonderful job
You did
And if they have some great improvements here
Then obviously i listen to you
Decision
And I call no listening to your decision
Reflected upon it after a day or so
and i'm very disappointed
Obviously, i don't like the ways
You all look right
If there is new business either
So
It hurts
As local businessman
It stings
And i'm not about it
I don't know what to say
But then, do you want me
To believe that the process is flawed
Believe taking a month or more
The listening of seven presentations
How could we expect anyone
Remember? What was said
And the first one or two presentations
We have to be in this second one
So i think even in reviewing some of your comments
It looked like that you felt
That way as well, I'm going put it towards you
Not just look about where after i read the comments
Believe its okay
To a question process
I think that our country was built on the premise
It's okay to question in a process
Believe it will work
And at first i wasn't sure
Because, unbelievable
But
You know?
We had several people with the same last name
That helped me
And i wanted to be with it
Because
Not because we had a chance of winning
But I didn't believe that is important for future
My name was business owners
We try and fix this process
It's flawed
Well, great people in my mind
Talk about these a lot
Many times talk
About very positive things
About growing in the city
We have really good hours of sleep
I'm lucky enough to be built
It's a cool place
To live and i want it
And even cooler places
For my kids, new kid
In regards
To go on
So we're asking you
Every effort
We have a lot of work
To be able to do this
For those who save our community
I've shown me sincerely hope
And what we expect that i am
The next time, like the first time
Before you ask about something much more positive
Like it's great, bond issue
Or something else
Thank You
Do you have any questions or other words?
We can't
I could address those issues when the agenda item comes out
Thank You
If we had a question, it's good that
That might be of staff if they don´t need to go
Thanks for your attention
Thank YOU
Any other public input comments
I have a number of fours
The staff is recommending
Originally items five through ten
But i think there was
A correction on item nine
So staff are recommending items
Five six seven eight and 10
And then we'll just deal with 9 separate
For the consent agenda
We will go to the first one
Alright
So
And in item nine, it will just a correction
It is approved contract with levy town for concert
At the coalman theater and that
The location of those has changed to buffalo rank as senos
With this act correct
Approved contract
For council
Concerts buffalo rank as senoron march third
To be held in conjunction
The anniversaries of the operation
Motion approved, most approve and a second
Well, call please?
Western
Aye
Okay that takes an eye on 11
Approved feeway
Resolution for contract with open on
A pet professionals
For a rental civic center gym
To be paid for the young adult show
And for the ladies come in and talk to you about this
My name is Gary Forbes, I'm a president of the Colman pet professionals
We've been here several years
In we'd like stay in Miami because it's close together surrounding states
There are many people coming from Kansas
In Missouri & Arkansas
Times were pretty tough on us
We rode on the finances to pay
One of these for building
And how many years would this make now that we have
The event has been held here at the Civic Center
Here recall
This is started before
I think it will be a lot more
Last year, when we get ready
Another building over by the turn bike gate
One of the Indian buildings
For commodity distributed and parking is horrible
And do you know why we didn't get into a last year's environment
What I was told, they were going to tell us about it
We paid or started over
Yeah
They're still researching
But let me take one because
We've got to be proved with the taxpayer dollars
I do remember now that there were several events
That we're deferred as a result of it
David under public purpose part
Of the agenda
Or objectives
Tell me about what all those are
It's an annual major
For we give it 5 scholarships of a year
Different number of prizes
And then they're going to commit the tax care
It's educational for all pedonyrs, operators
A lot in estate, site and museum
Or required
To get so many hours of education over here
And that's part of what we do
So it provides knowledge for our citizens, what is far more
It's free to the public
We're trying get a better and safer people over here
In addition around about being responsible
Put on animal control mayor
Both in positive and negative consequences
I think
The only concern i would have, sir
I'll speak for myself first, is the cleaning deposit
We don't have a problem put into it
Great
I mean we've always cleaned and not had
And i expect to be that way again
Or just trying make sure
Observe they're precise on everything those deposits
So, I'm understanding
Any other questions
I'm not a mayor
Make the most sure approved, we have a second
Roll call please
Johnson
Aye
Okay
Thank you very much
The deposit
OK
I am proud of proofy resolution and contract
With your mind, i thought it boosted your club for
For their annual poor port dinner
Mr. Strack
Yes sir
Good evening
Just wanted to get our
Way of approval
The way for resolution and contract
My wife, my wife
Head softball coach had baseball coach here at
I just got hired on this year
This is a fundraiser we do
For our programs
I both high school middle-school
You can program to help finance
To get resources we need in order
Give our student athletes the best possible
Chance went on field as well
Become positive members of
Our society here
Basically, were one two
Way for the
Reddle of the Senate
The Senate and the Bank of England
Worked directly with steep line on this
They have done it for
I believe when we had our meeting
With student athletes
Other day nine years
Last year was a first-year that they did do
Had to new baseball coach last
Year, my wife
He just given birth to her son
A bit of a skill went back to school in January
So didn't have the time
I guess, time constraints
To set that up last year
Last year they just did hold it
Sadly both
The baseball and softball program
Suffered by
Losing about
The 500 dollar deposit and issue
It's like a week
You can get it right back
No, if that is
That an issue we cannot handle
Motion or third version
Motion to answer
Johnson
Four-star
Good to go
Thank you. I am 13
For bond presentation
Dr James
Welcome to James is getting up and ready
To make his presentation
Could I ask that we quickly go back
Back-to-Hide of 10
It's gone
Back & forth
And it just texted a man
She could not do it
But, but
Is at the cold end
Okay
Has been buffalo run
Sorry, but
I'm just going about
Warrowsing two hours ago
We know we're right now
You have a number of amin
So this is being as much third
Do you want to
I mean quickly amend it or
Or can deal with that at the next meeting
The contract actually says that
Yeah so contracts okay
So I'm going to amend the motion on
Item number nine
To read
Go call
You should
I
Wester
Okay
The key factor
There's been moved around
That is where it confuses coming
But this was correct for
Mr. James
Thank you for being here
Welcome
We have with us
This is Donny Lone, our board president
Mr. Malsnarsel Walder
I'm going to address your own
Hi
Good
Thanks again for allowing me
To come to the council
Thank you
Of our school district, a new bond proposal
As are bonded to last time failed
We listened most important thing
And we have made revisions as needed
To cut cost is much
As much possible while still accomplishing
Our main goal which
Is safe and secure schools
Positive learning environments for staff
Much of the funds will go
To make sure that the funding is available
By creating entrances which will send guests into
The offices before entering
Building the accessing children
Security monitoring equipment
We'll be updated
Instead of a pitch street for high school
Like we wanted, we're doing
A flat redo
Of
Flet
All and as well, track locker rooms at the high school
And connecting our main building to
The Mac
Aswell is in the tech centre so that students do not leave
In close space
At any time during day
We'll also have its roof redone
We will closed
To be able
To go outside for security reasons
They're filled with house
The building is in the city
We'll still be
Building across
Atmicals
Campus and it will update
In and rework
With new showers
As well as
Lockers
We'll be gaining ADA
Restrooms and administrative areas
So that they can see also to people coming in the building
We're seeing Washington
In a row about three of our elementary schools
We will gain secured entrances as I've said
Connecting outside doors
To come into offices
Rootdale must have extra classroom space
As well as Nichols
We need extra spaces
As the upper elementary Nichols also need a highly functioning
Media centre which it really does not have at this point
That will be added to front of their building in that
You shape and very
Facing south
The paved
There'll probably pay being parking lots there
And I pick up drop-off area
At
So all these things
We'll be done on a budget
The bond issue is set at 3.6 million
And we will only increase your yearly
Will state tax by mere 7.53
Much lower than me had tried in the past
Knowing you're not getting that pie and sky
But,
If You are going to take tax
My amount of home
Is around $400 a year
It will increase by only 30
For the entire year
That's about 2.50 cents a month
The fortune at once
He is full of state tax that up behind
About 1,000 dollars
Increase to 75
Or less than 6
So
That'll be coming
We've got all information on being here in
He and the street seem to get
And let everybody know what we will be doing with that 3.6 million
Dollars
The vote schedule for
About 4,5
So April 5
We've got a couple of months
Between now
Where would this citizen
Get information on our website
Of course we will be having
Rectures with the company that
We contract
With it does all of our
Bonding capacity
Just like last time
They ate at last
We'll get information
If you would like a meeting
As to come and present any
With information, have flyers
To hand out
As you get
I'm a column diagrams, pictures
What ever gets
If we would like to come back at some point
We'd give closer and present that again
Or welcome me
Thank You, Mr.
Look it's your calendar
Think about the time
That might make them those cents
We want to be supportive of the community
And we know this is important
Thank you very much, you know
Schools are a really
Important part about our community
Only what's best for kids
Okay anything else if not
If thank You Very Much
I'm 13
Approved
Mayors recommendation
Mayors fire January 2nd of 19
We have a motion to approve
My nominee of Joe Deodol
Marks forward
Mr.
I'm 15
Resolution authorizing the transfer
First weapon and charge
To catch and fill up by
Do his retirement with a Miami police department
Put her in contract
That is a union mayor of KSIV
For contract when they were tired
They're working there, they are doing badge
Filmed in 25 years
He was going to be here at 9-2420
He retired from right work with the R9A post department
So he couldn't make it tonight
But that's what I want you to sign up
He was a great officer
You were also friends with him on Facebook
We hope he could be here tonight
In the future we're going to try and get them
Here's what they can say
Thank you for your time
I'm glad thankyou
Motion to approve my second
Well, Johnston, question
Four stars
All right
I am 16 discussion of recommendation
Health insurance committee
Thank you
Good evening
We're glad to be here
To talk about hiring and employment
This is a process that started over three years ago
So it's been in lot
A long time, we've got this morning thinking
It finally came into its culmination
And get the opportunity all
So the City of Malm has had this same third party administrator
Four 15-plus years benefit management out
Of John one
Our HLL record is being a bond for couch and loosen
Also, we have about 300 covered lives
That in Guarnar Health Plan
And that includes our employees
Retirees
I hope we like it said for three-plus years
Even before being came discussing what this means
With the implementation of The Affordable Health Care Act
What can be waning down on us
And i don't know how else to put
It is a whole bunch
Of regulations and compliance
About all those days
even though, We have Cindy
Being a worker who was our HR manager
In her benefits coordinator
She's a very technical field
And we knew that We needed some assistance
But I'm going to make sure
That is the same way for 15 years
Plus, she has something about us
To explore our options
With the rising cost of health care
We have to do something proactive
To make sure that we are managing those costs
And also on the flip side of
That, what you want get our employees
The best benefits can for WhatWe Can afford
So it happened as this in a long journey
A child leadership team decided
To move forward with an employee benefit broker
In one year health insurance broker
Employee benefits brokers
One more work we're talking about
We're going to help us with lots of different benefits
That we offer our employees
We sell off PR out in June 2014
And i want a thing that question clean
Because, the head was starting her team learning HR
She's done some extensive work on this process
Also it has been really appreciated
We got several responses from seven brokers
Those workers were in AP and she knew her son and associates
The ministers, author J Gallagher company, locked him
the insurance center
One blood benefit group, a bone for couch and a Wilson
Employee benefits broker community which consisted of municipal finance manager
Lindsay Schnauck & Berg
Sitting on a drinking cartoff
Myself as HR director
HR manager and benefits coordinator
Cindy being over in the we appreciated
Councilwoman Morgensen also serving with this same community
We are called on each broker
And allowed them to do a presentation
To committee, lower not at
The same amount of time for their presentations
This is a career from September 3rd December 2015
It was one bit lengthy process
Part that would be due
One broker that had a healthy shoe
And it has asked for three weeks extension before they could do their presentation and we allowed
But what we thought is each committee member doing
Each of those presentations
Had an notes summary sheet with the 10 criteria
That were considering
So as we run along in this process,
Each of us documented our notes from most presentations
At culmination above them
One way to about three-to four weeks
And none of us discussed it with each other
In we scored, based on those criteria
There was a scoring system that
We had set up and then came back together
To determine what our final recommendation is going
The committee unanimously decided
To recommend NFP machine or Hedelson in associates
They were the decision involved five people
On their community they scored
The highest
And that is our recommendation to you this evening
For approval as are employee benefit broker
One of the major contributing factors with them
Was a experience they have
With municipal accounts
They had over 35 in Oklahoma
Also we did check references
We didn't know Check all
Of those references from everyone
But at least two-to four
From each other seven brokers
And from those references
That helped us also derive some of our decision
If the recommendation and this is a discussion item
But whatever they decide to hire
The process would be asking me
To give you authority to negotiate
A contract which we will begin working on immediately
As soon as that's completed
We can bring it back
The contract will be a two-year-old model
With the first year having to have a renewal clause in it
In 2 years, this city of London level once again
Go through work or evaluation process
To determine what best options are for their City
We look consistently every ten
Years go Through This Process Moving forward
So that we can make sure That
Week keep out with Whatthe Cities needs Are
I've told Deanness Before
I think this is one of the biggest decisions
That we make as a Charter
And then say that because
It has so much
A blendy
Give him The Immology
When i have a cold, if it's a heart attack
If you're hiring benefits specialist
Let us help to explain what we need on compliance side
And also what they did down into our data
Laydown All of their options
So that we can make the best decision weekend for What We Can afford
That's really only half an 15 years in a month
I just want to say i appreciate all of them
But certainly on The Committee
They'll take it very seriously
This is important decision
So i'm not reading, speak to that
Actually Kim
What we've always tried To point out is That there were five people on this group looking at it
We are all 5 Engels and how he did
And so I think you're going
You know what's up
Any questions?
A lot of packet was
I told Dean a KL2O
It has been visual aid.
I mean, somebody that i have won a list for the last year
So it means any questions about anything
That you're one and nine for me
Well if there's a question
Very curious About how
Our plan is going to evolve
Self-funded versus non self funded
And we'll be looking For some guidance
Another two very different paths
And in the past
I always believed that self funded was
Was it a better city's best to enter
But i believe It has been
With all of The walls and changes these days if they still is or not
Right,
We have some convincing that it's still not in your best interest
One of the positives is That with a CIA we were granted to be because
Were self funded
But what I'm doing here Is hiring a professional To lay out all over options
So, now i can't legitimately tell you whether
It was just a waste or not Because
But yeah, it's going to be Interesting To see what the options are
And we all discussed that
You know when you don't go self-funded
If i give up a little bit of control and That is A difficult thing
In real our plan
We managed It well.
I've had couple Of Refereers but thats
So kind LAY OUT What will happen over The next several months
Because if decisions can make by July 1
We have to be in place by July 1
And we start our July one
That's only really 4 months
You know, 45 minutes
Even if when you don't make some kind of A significant change
that being Whether In RTPLA or network
In July we still have the option that We can do it in January
So, one of those periods But One Of The Things
Re-asked NFP and they feel strongly They Can Get us to Where
And be by July 1
So instantly Once
It's a contract is approved
Let me start giving them data for Lots
Of Years and Digging Down Pretty Quickly
They've indicated Within About Six Weeks
Think they Can Have Something Back To Us
I want to make a comment And all of you about One City that
In Fee has in That's Mescogi
Had A lot of conversations with the HR Director
In Mescogi, their plan was Actually The Negative
Has Never had an Insurance Broker
That was Kind of Similar to What We Are Now
In a Young Half, They're Now To Me Into The Good
And they've had significant savings By Going With Blue Cross and Blue Shield
But the comment that she made It Mean Was
I Feel strongly Not Worked For Us
but NFP is going Back How You And Much Know what Works for you
Think we'll kind Of Tip The Hat
For The Community was Just That They Have So Much
Municipal Experience
Doing the City's Exactly Like Us
Cities that are Larger Talsa
Came Of Your References You Said Two To Four
Were they All Minus Palettes or Some of Their Referances Other Than
Minus Palette?
Was Most Of What The References Are Given
I Know The Private Second References Actually Have Just Come In
in the Last Week
As For Us Employee's They Were All Pretty Poisoned
Some Roger.
Some Roger?
Some Significantly Smaller
And NFP Has Glove That Was A Positive Reference for Them
Unless they Are Pretty Moors, So We Had Positive Referances
That Was A Number Two In The Scoring
And the Scoring Sheets Are In
Packet and Gallagher Head Positive References Also
But Ultimately When We Looked All Of
Teng Criteria
Namelessly, we Just felt Like This was
Best Option ForThe City of My Emma
So I'm Stasped Made It Work
Remindation that Falls Us To Accept
The Reclamation or Directing To Go A Different
I'm Supposedly As This Agenda
To Be Listed For Discussion Only
Because There Are Several Hundred Pages Here
Want to Make Sure That Any Council Member
One At More Time
Two Review The Information Had That Time
So, Well Say With At least Rich
On behalf of Gallagher
In The Claim That He I Love There With Draw
And he's A Drain Out
Exactly Had To Take that
Think the Issue Is Important
We Could Do It, Don't Know What You Can Do
Any Where One But If Its Tax Pair Dollars
So if we Got At Last Year
So I Don't Want Us To Take A Long Time
And Councilman ForSTERS Going to Be Out Of The Country
At Our Next Regular Meeting
What i Would Like
Is Have a Meeting Next Tuesday
Which We Will Make A Decision
That's My Recommendation
Does Anybody Wanna Do Anything Differently Than that?
No It's My With Me.
Okay Within We Will Meet Again Next Tuesday
And we will Make A Reckon In Dation
Thank You
Your Audit Would you Like To Follow The Four Of You Are Here
So At Time Since Its Especially
I Don't Have my Calendar with me
Is There a Time That's By The Plot
Or For Everybody Typically
You Put Me On The Sponsor
What Is That?
Not Just My Back On Comment
In I Respect Courage Over It Very Much
A Like Courage
When He Said Its Was Floored
i Don't Know What he Means By That
Always l Can Tell you Us Five Being Together
it was very, on the Up and Up
There's a Very Service And We Took It Serious
And The Money Met By the Word Floored
My Interpretation That It Was At Just Any Time You Have
A Lengthy Lgged
Can To Be What Length He Means But a Lengthy Lgged
In Between We Get Some Information
Make A Decision On it
Thats NotThe Ideal
That Is It Mean The Decision Was
Impacted Thats A Gnaficking
Brian and Two Star Works For Me
Soccer 9-6
That's Eight of All Basketball
So Five of Plots Used To LH
If You Would Post That Please
Try to Keep it Short But if There Are Other Things
Then We Will Do Those Also
Remember Brian is Going Be Out Of the Country Second
The Next Meeting So
Okay, Thank You
And Thanks Everybody On It Can Be
the Neal Cindy
Everyone That Sort Of
I Don't Seven Jeanne New Business Dean
Another New Business Any Other New Business
No Your Honor
If Not We Are To Met Or In Council of Community & Outstress
We Can Be Out Of Congratulations to Your Life as Well
Because That's Wonderful So we Had a Very Good Time At The Chamber
Bank With And Is A good To Have Our Community
Recognized As That On It.
I Want You to Bring That Up
Okay, Thank you
In Item 21 Executive Session For Surrends
And 3-0 7 E
We Have Emotion To Go In The Executive Session For the Reasons
Listed in The Agenda
Most In Going Exetuations My Second Place
Second
Second.
Two Minutes
22 is Municipal Attorney David Anderson
Con Track and As we Talk About
Contract and Place
It needs a Slide Momma For Cation To Put The 30 Day Notice
Provision in There If You'll Take Get That Done
And Send it Out.
We Will Be Good to Go
Item 21 is A John May we Have Emotion To A John
Point Of Clad of Creation on Our Reasons
Make that Next Tuesday
Yeah, Okay
I'll Make Sure Thats On Next Two
David's Contracts On Next 2
SoWe Can Vote
With The Miner Modification On
Okay, I Need To Get
Motor off.
Alright?
So We Are To Item 23 You Have Emotion to A John
Motion To a Journey Second
Roke All
Forster, Johnson, Sting, Shel
7 2 3 5 E
He's That Pop